Guide to the Harold and Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz Public Art Archive 1961-2009 (bulk 1976-2005) MSS.171
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Administrative Files
  - Grand Rapids: Press, 1996, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - G.S.A., 1992, 1995-1996 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - G.S.A. Mandate for Publication, 1975-1991 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Hara Museum Arc, undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Hersh Farms, undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Hickory Sculpture Competition, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Hoffman Gallery Exhibition, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - High Line, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Hospital Art, 1996-1997 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Hudson: Scenic, [undated] (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Images, [undated] (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - IMP- Stationary, [undated] (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Independent Curators, [undated] (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Insignia/ESG Art Ideas- Photography, 1987; 2001 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Insignia/ESG Art Ideas- Miscellaneous, 2001; [undated] (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Insignia/ESG Art Ideas- Brenda Zlamany, 1994-2001; [undated] (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Institute for Research in Art- University of South Florida, 2001-2003 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Institute for Urban Design, [undated] (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - International Association for Professional Advisors, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial, 2000-2002 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial, 2000-2009 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- "Irish Hunger Design Team" Brian Tolle, 2000-2001; [undated] (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- JPS Projects Brian Tolle, [undated] (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- Correspondence with Artists, 2000-2001; [undated] (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- "HC BPCP Fees", 1993; 2000; [undated] (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- "Irish Hunger Articles", 2000-2001; [undated] (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- "Irish H Press", 2000-2001; [undated] (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- JPS Projects; Brian Tolle slides and photographs, [undated] (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- JPS Projects, 2000-2001; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- JPS Projects Proposals, 1999; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- Brian Tolle, 1997; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- Press Irish Hunger, 2001; [undated[ (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- Press Clips, 2001-2002; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- Brian Tolle, 2001-2005; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- Brian Tolle, 2001-2002; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- Brian Tolle, 2003-2006; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- Brian Tolle Slides/Photographs, 1997-2005; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- Brian Tolle "2002", 2000-2002 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- Loose Materials, 2001-2002; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Irish Hunger Memorial- Design presentation and loose materials, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - ISC Trustee, [undated] (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Italy and Rome, 2003; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - J. Kaufman: Kotobuki, 1994; 2003 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - J. Mondale- JPS Pari Lecture, 1994; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Jack Brogan Contract, 1996-1997; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Japan: AACA, 1993; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Japan: American Center, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Japan: Architects, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Japan: Ashihara, Y., 1994 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Japan: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Japan: Higuchi, S., 1992-1994; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Japan: Kataoka, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Japan: Kotobuki, 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Japan: Kotobuki, 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Japan: Lecture Tour, 1992-1993; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Japan: Museums, 1992-1994; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Japan: P.A.R.I. Public Art Research Institute, 1994-1996 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Japan: P.A.R.I. Public Art Research Institute [Miya Yoshida], 2003 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Japan: Press, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Japan: Public Art, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Japan: Sculpture, 1993; [undated] (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Japan: Travel, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Japan: Tour 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Japan: Untitled, [undated] (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - JFK Contract, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - JFK Expenses, 1996-1997; 2005-2007 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - JFK Oppenheim, 1998 (Box 41, Folder data_value_missing_a7ec79b4738367562b0f0e42dc9d91b4)
  - JFK Other Sites, 1986-2004 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - JFK - Postponed, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - JPS Artwork, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - JPS Exhibitions, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - JPS Exhibitions, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - JPS Fees, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - JPS Japan Trip, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - JPS Lectures [1 of 2], undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - JPS Lectures [2 of 2], undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - JPS Letters of Recommendation, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - JPS Long Resume, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - JPS LTD. Proposals, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - JPS Project Associates, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - JPS Project Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - JPS Project Summaries, undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - JPS Proposals, undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - JPS Proposals, undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - JPS References, undated (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - JPS Services, undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - JPS Short Bios, undated (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - JPS Short Resume, undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - JPS Slide Presentations, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - JPS Staff: Resumes, undated (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - JPS Works of Art for Public Spaces, undated (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Kansas City: Percent for Art, undated (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Kansas City: Public Art, undated (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Kansas City Project - Public Art Fund, undated (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Kansas City Project - Public Art Fund, undated (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Kansas City Scuplture: Henry Moore, undated (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Kansas City - R. Morris - Bull Wall, undated (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Kansas City - Untitled, undated (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Kozloff - San Francisco, undated (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Kotobuki, undated (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Kotobuki - Animal Sculpture, undated (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Kotobuki - Correspondence, undated (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Kotobuki - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Kotobuki - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Kotobuki - Iwate Prefecture, undated (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Kotobuki - Kaufman [1 of 2], undated (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Kotobuki - Kaufman [2 of 2], undated (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Kotobuki - Madsen, undated (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Kotobuki - Miyagi Prefectual University, undated (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Kotobuki - Mullican/University Project, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Kotobuki - Nigata Hospital/Kaufman, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Kotobuki - Notsuda High School, undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Kotobuki - Oita Cultural Hall, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Kotobuki - Potential Projects, 1996-1997 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Kotobuki - Sugarman, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Kotobuki - Tabuchi, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Landscape Architect, undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Landscaping American Gardens, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Landscaping European Gardens, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Landscaping National Parks, undated (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Landscaping Oriental Gardens, undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Landscaping Private Gardens, undated (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - La Salle, undated (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - La Salle, undated (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - La Salle, undated (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - La Salle '93 - Fed/Res, undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - La Salle '94 Lists / Janet's Lists, undated (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - La Salle '97 catalogue, undated (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - La Salle - 2nd Show P.R., undated (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - La Salle (1 of 2) Consign '96, undated (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - La Salle (2 of 2) Consign '95 Letters, undated (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - La Salle - 3rd Ex. Correspondence, undated (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - La Salle Four Seasons, undated (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - La Salle - Pricelists, undated (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Law & Seattle - Guidelines, undated (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Legal Files - Hoffman, B., undated (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Location One, undated (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Loren Masden Correspondence 1 of 2, undated (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Loren Masden Sculpture Info 2 of 2, undated (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Los Angeles, undated (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Los Angeles - Subway Art, undated (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Lower Manhattan Development Corporation, undated (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Madsen, Loren - Contracts, undated (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Madsen, Loren - Contract Correspondence, undated (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Madsen, Loren - Fabrication/Ship, undated (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Madsen, Loren - Financial 1997 (invoices, wire [advances]), undated (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Marfa, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Materials, undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Mattress Factory, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Mayer (Frany-Gabriel), undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Memorials, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Memorials, undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Memorials 9/11 World Trade Press, undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Memorials 2000-01, undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Memorials 2002, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Memorials - Memphis Civil Rights 2001-02, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Memphis Art Council, undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Metro Art Ephemera [1 of 2], undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Metro Art Ephemera [2 of 2], undated (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Metro - Dade: Miami, undated (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Metropolis, undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Authority, undated (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Milwaulkee Proposal [1 of 2], undated (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Milwaulkee Proposal [2 of 2], undated (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Minnesota, undated (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Misc., undated (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Misc, undated (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Untitled [Misc.], undated (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Untitled [Misc.], undated (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Misc Info., undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Miya Visit 10/26-11/2/96, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Miya Yoshida Correspondence, undated (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Modern Works, undated (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Monographs Artists Registry '99, undated (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - MTA, undated (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - MTA Arts for Transit - 2007 - 2nd Avenue Subway, undated (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Mullican, Matt, undated (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Mullican, Matt - Contract, undated (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Mullican - Correspondence, undated (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Mullican - Proposal, undated (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Untitled [Multimedia], undated (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Multiples Art Foundry, undated (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Munster, undated (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Murals, undated (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Musei Civici Veneziani, undated (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Museums are Public Spaces, undated (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Nation 2005 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - National Museum of Women in the Arts, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - National Museum of Women in the Arts, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - NC Arts, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - NCBC - Tampa [1 of 3], undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - NCBC - Tampa (Taiwan) [2 of 3], undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - NCBC - Tampa (Lecture in Taiwan) [3 of 3], undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - NCBC - Tampa (Tower Project), undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - NEA / Culture Wars, undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - New Rochelle, undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - New York Arts in Transit, undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - New York Arts in Transit, undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - New York City Tours, undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - New York - New Visions, undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - New York / Tokyo '94, undated (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - NY Public Art Network - NY PAN, undated (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - New York University, undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - New York University - International Council, undated (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - News from UK - Public Art 2007, undated (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - News Stands, undated (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - NMWA - Florida Artists' Exhibit Controversy, undated (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - NOAA, undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Not Vital - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, etc., undated (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Not Vital - Reviews, undated (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Oaklahoma Memorial, undated (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Oliver Sculpture Ranch, undated (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Orlando 2005, undated (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Orlando - Creative City Project 2001-2004, undated (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Orlando - L.R.T. Press, undated (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Orlando - Light Rail Information, undated (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Orlando LRT: Artists, undated (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Orlando Light Rail, undated (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Orlando LRT Second Artist Call, undated (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Orlando LRT 6/5/99 Expenses, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Orlando LTR Contract, undated (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Other Artist Info Forms, undated (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Pace, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Pace Wildenstein 2008-9 China (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Packing/Shipping Info, undated (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Palm Beach, 1997, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Palm Springs, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Palma de Mallorca, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Park Avenue - Leger, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - Port of Oakland, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Partners for Livable Communities, undated (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Partners Creative Cities, 2001-2004 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - Party List '96, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Past collection - Insignia ESG, undated (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Peekskill, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - Peekskill - 1995, 1993-1995 (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - Peekskill Artists, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Peekskill: Budgets, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Peekskill Columbia Program, undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Peekskill Exhibition 1996, 1994-1996 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Peekskill Existing, undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Peekskill Expenses, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Peekskill Expense 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Peekskill Funding, 1996-1999 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Peekskill Fundraising, undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Peekskill Fundraising, undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Peekskill History, undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Peekskill IBM, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Peekskill Ideas, 1998-1999 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Peekskill Kaplan, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Peekskill - Lutz Contract, 1993-1999 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Peekskill Munster, 1995-1998 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Peekskill Munster, 1995-1999 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Peekskill on Web, undated (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Peekskill Plans, undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Peekskill Press, undated (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Peekskill Project, undated (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Peekskill Plans, undated (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Peekskill Proposal, undated (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Peekskill Proposal, undated (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Peekskill Tape Art, undated (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Peekskill Warhol Foundation, 1998-1999 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Penn Station - Master Plan Proposal, undated (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Penn Station, 2001-2003 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Percent for Art, undated (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Percent for Art, 1980-1991 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Percent for Art, 1983-1992 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Percent for Art '94, '95, '96, 1994-1996 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Percent for Art: Alaska, undated (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Percent for Art: California, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Percent for Art: Cambridge, undated (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Percent for Art: Laws U.S.A., undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Percent for Art: LMCC, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Percent for Art: NYC, undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Percent for Art: Seattle, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Percent for Art: Transportation, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Percent for Art & RDA: Philadelphia, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Percent for Art: Untitled, undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Performa (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Philadelphia, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Philadelphia - Buttonwood, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Phoenix, undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Phoenix, Arizona, undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Phoenix Arts Commission, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Photos - Historic, undated (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Pittsburgh, undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Pittsburgh Airport - Artists, undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Pittsburgh Airport - Color Article, undated (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Pittsburgh Airport - Correspondence, undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Pittsburgh Airport - Photographs, undated (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Pittsburgh Airport - Press, undated (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Pittsburgh Airport - Project, undated (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Pittsburgh Airport - Project Photographs & Artist Contracts [includes CD of photos], undated (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Places, undated (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Polich Art Works, undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Politics & Art, undated (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - PPS - Projects for Public Spaces, undated (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Press & Info Kits @ Public Art, undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Press Lists 1999-2000, undated (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Prints [1 of 4] - Don Gummer, undated (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Prints [2 of 4] - Print Gallery, undated (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Prints [3 of 4] - PSA Wack!!, undated (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Prints [4 of 4], undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Private Eye - Reprints, undated (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Professionals for Non-Profits, undated (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Projects Completed, undated (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Projects in Progress, undated (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Proposal for Florida Atlantic University, undated (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Proposal Phoenix Sky Harbor Center, undated (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Proposal for Public Art, Kansas City, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - PS1 2000, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - PSG Framing, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Public Art, undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Public Art, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Public Art, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Public Art, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Public Art, undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Public Artworks, undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Public Art 1988, undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Public Art 1990, undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Public Art 1994, undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Public Art 1997, undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Public Art 2000, undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Public Art 2001, undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - 2009, undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Public Art Advocacy 1996, undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Public Art Articles 1994-95, undated (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Public Art Articles 1995-96, undated (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Public Art - Barcelona, undated (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Public Art - Barcelona, undated (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Public Art - Bibliography, undated (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Public Art - Civic Lists, undated (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Public Art Connection, undated (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Public Art Connection, undated (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Public Art Contemporary 2006, undated (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Public Art - Controversy, undated (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Public Art Controversy 1994-95, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Public Art Controversy 1996 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Public Art Controversy 1997-98, 1997-1998 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Public Art Controversy, undated (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Public Art Controversy, undated (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Public Art Education, undated (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Public Art - Ethnic, undated (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Public Art - Exhibition, undated (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Public Art Forum, undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Public Art Forum, undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Public Fountains, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Public Art Fund, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Public Art Fund, undated (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Public Art Gardens, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Public Art Gardens, undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Public Art - General, undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Public Art Handout, undated (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Public Art - History, undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Public Art Law, undated (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Public Art: Los Angeles, undated (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Public Art: Los Angeles, undated (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Public Art: Los Angeles, Policy, undated (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Public Art: Miami, undated (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Public Art: Monuments, undated (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Public Art Network, undated (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Public Art News, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Public Art Fund NYC, undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Public Art Opportunities, undated (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Public Art Organizations, undated (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Public Art Organization, undated (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Public Art: Photos, undated (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Public Art: Photos, undated (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Public Art: Photos, undated (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Public Art: Photos, undated (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Public Art: Planning, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Public Art Politics, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Public Art Process, undated (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Public Art Research Institute, undated (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Public Art Research Institute, undated (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Public Art Research: Japan Higuchi Article, undated (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Public Art Review, undated (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Public Art - Sculpture, undated (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Public Spaces, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Public Spaces & Public Art International Conference, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Public Art Transportation, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Public Art Program Planning Report, undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Public Art: WPA, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Public Art: Untitled, undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Public Art: Untitled, undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Public Art: Untitled, undated (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Public Art: Untitled, undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Public Art: Untitled (Proposals), undated (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Publicolor, undated (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Queens Plaza Proposal, undated (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Real Estate & Art, undated (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Real Estate Investments, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Registries - Other NYU Public Art, undated (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Retail: MOMA, undated (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Robinson - Vietnam Book, undated (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Rockefeller Center, undated (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Rockefeller Center, undated (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Roosevelt Island Correspondence, undated (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Roosevelt Island ROC, undated (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Roosevelt Island Waterfront Drawings, undated (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco, undated (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Santa Fe, undated (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Santa Monica, undated (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Sasaki, undated (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Save Outdoor Sculpture, undated (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Screen Saver - RD, undated (Box 50, Folder 27A)
  - Sculpture Center, undated (Box 50, Folder 27B)
  - Sculpture Garden, undated (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Sculpture Gardens, undated (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Sculpture: Gen. Mills, undated (Box 50, Folder 30A)
  - Sculpture Goes Public - New York Times, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 30B)
  - Sculpture: Hakone, undated (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Sculpture Parks & Gardens: Central Park, undated (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Sculpture Parks & Gardens: Cranbrook, undated (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Sculpture Parks & Gardens: First Ladies' Garden, undated (Box 50, Folder 34)